yesvideo.com 2012-09-20

# YesVideo | Privacy Policy

This YesVideo Privacy Policy (or "Privacy Policy") explains the practices and policies of YesVideo, Inc. ("YesVideo") regarding the collection and protection of Personal Data (defined below) supplied by users or collected by us from users of the YesVideo digital conversion, online hosting, and sharing on this site (the "Service"). By accessing or using the Service, you agree (1) to comply with the terms and conditions of this YESVIDEO Privacy Policy and (2) YesVideo may process (i.e., collect, use, etc.) your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy or IN the Terms and Conditions of Use. 

YesVideo defines "Personal Data" as any data from which it is practical to directly determine the identity of an individual. This Privacy Policy is entered into in conjunction with the YesVideo Terms and Conditions of Use. This Privacy Policy may be updated by YesVideo from time to time. YesVideo will provide notice of materially significant changes to the Privacy Policy by changing the Revision Date of this Privacy Policy, posting notice on its site(s), and/or sending a notice directly to users registered email address. A user's continued use of or access to the Service following such notice signifies the user's intent to be bound to such change or changes. 

**HOW INFORMATION IS USED**

**Personal Data**

Personal Data may be used for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the Service, (iv) to better understand users' needs and interests, (v) to fulfill requests users may make, (vi) to personalize users' experience, and (vii) to provide or offer updates and/or Service announcements.Â  We may also use Personal Data to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by us or third parties ("Marketing Communications"). If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive any such Marketing Communications, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in any of the communications sent to you, or update your "account settings" information. 

We will not sell or market the email addresses or other collected personal information of registered users to third parties. We will not view the files that you upload using the Service, unless reasonably required for monitoring purposes (see our Terms and Conditions of Use). We may view your file system information to provide technical support. You acknowledge and agree that YesVideo may occasionally send you administrative communications regarding your account or the Service via email. 

**Cookies and Passive Data Collection**

YesVideo uses cookies, IP addresses, and URLs to improve and further develop the Service, and to provide enhanced features to users, where available. YesVideo uses cookies to save user names, session validators, and on users' browsers and hard drives, and may use them to provide tailored products and services to those users, as they become available. In addition, YesVideo may use cookies to authenticate the user on each page after the user logs on to the site. You may instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use all portions or functionality of the Service.Â  IP addresses also help us to diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Service, and to otherwise provide the Service to our users. We use information we obtain by these technical means for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service's technical administration, to increase the Service's functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to users' needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and site use behavior of our users, and to verify that users meet the criteria required to process their use or requests.

**Surveillance**

YesVideo disclaims any intention to censor, edit, or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by users or others. YesVideo will, however, review, delete, or block access to communications that may harm YesVideo, its users or other third parties. The grounds on which YesVideo may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of the YesVideo Terms and Conditions of Use or of this YesVideo Privacy Policy.

**WHICH INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

**Personal Data**

Once you register with YesVideo and sign in to the Service, you are not anonymous to YesVideo. When registering for the YesVideo Service, you provide Personal Data, which may include, without limitation, name, phone number, address, city, state, country, zip code, a user name, email address, user name and a password, information request data and response data. When uploading data or information to the Service, you send us such data but you may also be sending file system information, including names of files and directories. YesVideo may also record your IP address when you submit information. YesVideo also may collect, at your option, certain preference and demographic information from you.  
We track usage data and user traffic patterns throughout our site(s) to improve the Service. This information is collected to help improve site flow and usability. In addition, we track click-through information (including IP addresses). We may correlate your Personal Data with your usage data for specific circumstances, including but not limited to, security reasons, for purposes of providing customer service, or to track down a specific problem related to a specific user's use of the Service.

All information collected by YesVideo is used for internal purposes of providing the Service, providing support to users, and to improve the Service. Aggregating non-identifying information supplied by users allows YesVideo to understand its user base and to improve its Service. This aggregated data may be disclosed to third parties, but will not be connected to your Personal Data. By accessing and using our protected and secured sites, you agree to maintain the confidentiality of the user name and password you selected to access such site(s), and you also consent to our Terms and Conditions of Use.

All users may opt to remove their Personal Data from our live database by contacting YesVideo and canceling their YesVideo user account, although your Personal Data and other information may be retained in our archive or backup records.   
Consistent with the federal Children's Online Privacy Act of 1998 (COPPA), YesVideo does not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of 13. Any person who provides their Personal Data to YesVideo through the Service represents and warrants that they are 13 years of age or older. 

**Email Communications**

YesVideo may store users' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications.   
**  
Cookies and Passive Data Collection**

See above Section, also entitled "Cookies and Passive Data Collection."Â  As set forth above, YesVideo automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including without limitation, your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.Â  Users should also be aware that other websites visited before entering the YesVideo Service site(s) might place Personal Data within a user's URL during a visit to their website, and YesVideo has no control over such other websites. Accordingly, some of this information may be logged by YesVideo.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

YesVideo websites may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites may or may not have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting the websites. We have no responsibility for linked websites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our users.

**DISCLOSURES**

**YesVideo Partners and Affiliates**

YesVideo may disclose users' Personal Data to third party business partners or affiliates who provide specific services to the user along with the Service (such as hosting or other support services). Such third party business partner or affiliate may have their own privacy policies, and if YesVideo discloses the third parties name to the user, it is your responsibility to read and adhere to such policies. However, if we disclose your Personal Data to a third party business partner or affiliate that you are reasonably unaware of, then YesVideo will require that such third party's privacy policy is at least as strong as YesVideo's; otherwise, users will be provided with a mechanism to opt-out of having their Personal Data viewed by such third parties.

**Law Enforcement; Subpoenas**

YesVideo may disclose Personal Data, including the information or data uploaded to the Service, with or without notice (a) if required by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order, (b) where required by law, or (c) at our sole discretion, where we deem it necessary to protect the safety of any individual or the general public or to prevent violation of our Terms and Conditions of Use, this Privacy Policy or the rights of YesVideo or any third party.

**Change of Ownership**

In the event of a change in ownership (including through bankruptcy), or a merger, acquisition or sale of assets with or to another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of the YesVideo user information, including Personal Data, to such separate entity. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you (by posting on our site or an email to the email address you provide when you register) of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of the YesVideo Service assets by a third party, and you may choose to modify any of your registration information at that time. 

**Email Communications**

The circumstances under which YesVideo may disclose user electronic communications are when: (i) it is necessary in order to provide the Service to the user; (ii) it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of YesVideo, its users or third parties'; (iii) it is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants or other legal process that YesVideo determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and/or (iv) it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by YesVideo and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime that, in YesVideo's reasonable opinion, has not yet been reported.

**International Transfers**

Personal Data may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which YesVideo or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using or accessing the Service, you consent to any such transfer of Personal Data outside of your country.Â 

**SECURITY**

YesVideo uses industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the YesVideo Service in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, such as using SSL security measures, YesVideo cannot guarantee complete security. Further, while we take reasonable steps to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" or "crackers" from obtaining this information.

**UPDATING OR REMOVING USER INFORMATION**

You may, at any time, choose to correct, update or remove the information you have submitted to YesVideo by updating your account on our site.Â  However, even if you terminate your account, bear in mind that your Personal Data and other information may be retained in our archive or backup records. You may also opt out of receiving marketing communications by sending a request with your contact information to [support@yesvideo.com](mailto:lsupport@yesvideo.com).Â  Please note, however, that YesVideo reserves the right to send bulletins and other important information regarding the Service at our own discretion. 

**PRIVACY QUESTIONS AND CONTACTING YESVIDEO**

If you have an issue with respect to privacy regarding the YesVideo Service, we kindly ask that you attempt first to resolve the issue directly by contacting YesVideo.Â  In addition, users with questions about this Privacy Policy and any of the statements herein may contact YesVideo, in the following ways:

**E-Mail**  

**Post**  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
YesVideo, Inc.  
3281 Scott Boulevard  
Santa Clara, CAÂ  95054

**OTHER LEGAL NOTICES**

This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy for the YesVideo Service, and it supersedes any earlier version. Our YesVideo Terms and Conditions of Use take precedence over any conflicting YesVideo Privacy Policy provision. If any provision in this Privacy Policy is held to be unenforceable or invalid, all other provisions will remain in force, and such invalid provision shall be interpreted in order to affect the intent as closely as possible. 

_Revision Date: August 15, 2012_
